So the PCB that you are seeing here is
of Haier company, okay
and
what happens in it is that its
sensor is
placed around 20 and this sensor is
around 9 or 10, so there is a huge
difference between the two, so while I keep saying again and again that the
voltage should be 50%, so for that
if you look at any PCB,
I have already explained it in PF,
for this one's PCB, you
can check here, if you see here, it is
placed at 20
and here at
3.3, so this is of room charge sensor and
this one of room sensor has been
placed like this and there is no motor also, so there is
continuous light in it, it will not come on continuously, it will go
blank for some time, that
means this light will go off and will come on again, so
in that condition you will not be able to understand
and will say that the output is not coming,
whereas in this it was shown that the output is not coming, so
first of all what do you have to
check, you will definitely check
these things, you will check the
sensors etc.
here  But if the voltage drops after installing the sensor, then
your
one more problem will be that after 3 minutes,
heat these sensors a little,
as if you will heat
and keep checking at both the points of this sensor, then the voltage will
start dropping,
in that condition it should turn on, if it does
not turn on despite this then what will you have to do, at that
time you have to
check the voltage at both the points of the relay,
if it does not turn on then while searching it,
one of
these points will definitely be connected to the positive, you should search its second point
here, where is it connected to the
ground, that is,
if you assume that it has come here then
you should
click on it with the help of tweezers, then it will
really make a ticking sound,
if the
voltage is not coming then it is going wrong, then it
means that the relay is bad, if the voltage is not coming
and
after installing it it makes a sound, then
for this,
our ground is exactly opposite to this, if you
check the voltage here, then between
two and a half to five volts, then the
board should be five volts.  The controller of the micro will
run, approximately that much voltage will come here,
if the voltage that is supplied is not going out, that
means negative will come out from this,
keep this in mind, it is
crossed, so if negative is not crossed
and there is supply here, then the boiler is
bad, if
this is also not getting voltage here, then
next you sit and think, let's
check the microcontroller and the boiler, if there is no resistance in between, then the
resistance and
PF are not shorted because PF are
connected to the ground, so if there is no
shorting and no resistance is connected
directly to the controller, then there are
two things that can happen here, one is a
fault from the microcontroller's side, second
it is not getting any of our inputs, which should throw an error,
then our motor starts buzzing, the motor does
not work,
its feedback is divided here,
like if you see here, it has become ground,
its P, this is the positive supply and this
is out, so if you see this, the out
supply is pulled from 5 volts and
this is from 513 i.e. 51 kilo ohm  It has been told that there will
not be a 5 volt supply from a 5 volt supply in Anis, our socket will
not be connected to the motor, it will get time here
and the same 5 volt is
given to the micro controller from here directly, I will
make the same thing for you in the diagram, what
happens is that when there is 5 volt in it, then
when our motor cries, then two things happen, there is a
socket inside it, inside the socket,
see here there are
three wires, right
now if I talk about this circuit, then it is installed like this, so
according to that,
this blue color, yellow color which is visible, yellow
color, has a plus supply in it, the
voltage will come out from the middle one which is blue
and this one which is last here below, has a
negative supply
in the brown one,
if you can check this motor,
I will check and show you, so what it will do
here is that in the middle when
this motor turns, it will convert the
supply into such a thing,
on the child also, if the supply comes to me in the same way, then it will become
such, once it will
ground it, then after this it will leave it
Then I ground it, the faster it
runs, the smaller it starts becoming
and the slower it runs, the smaller it will
become, meaning it will remain on for half the time, it will remain off for half the time,
you will keep it on for half the time, if it is entered on the
credit card machine, then I
give it to you like this.